Where are we
우리를 어디
thai police
태국 경찰
Now I suspect you've reached your limit
이제 한계에 도달한 것 같습니다.
within national borders
국경 내에서
What? Is there espionage?
무엇? 간첩이 있나요?
did you take it
가져갔어?
Sample bottles to the border
국경까지 샘플 병
if
만약에
Isn’t this the mission of the game?
이게 이 게임의 미션 아닌가요?
answer my question
내 질문에 대답
if i say
내가 말하면
Will it break?
깨질까요?
game over
게임 끝
answer my question
내 질문에 대답
Bounds entered with the sample
표본과 함께 입력된 경계
What is your goal?
당신의 목표는 무엇입니까?
I do not know anything
나는 아무것도 모른다
You are wrong
당신은 잘못
Do you think you can be fooled?
속일 수 있다고 생각하시나요?
honestly
솔직히
i am confident of success
나는 성공을 확신한다
This round has been decided
이번 라운드는 결정됐어요
I can tell you what you said
당신이 말한 것을 말해 줄 수 있어요
Is what you said true or false?
당신이 말한 것이 사실인가요, 거짓인가요?
What's this
이게 뭐야?
What's your job?
당신의 직업은 무엇입니까?
next question
다음 질문
Please answer truthfully
사실대로 답변해주세요
It's a lying device
거짓말을 하는 장치야
take it
가져
I am not very good
나는 별로 좋지 않다
If you lie, you will feel uncomfortable
거짓말을 하면 기분이 나빠진다
Can I ask you a question?
질문해도 될까요?
The girl who came with me before
예전에 같이 왔던 여자
that girl
그 소녀
you have no right to ask
당신은 물어볼 권리가 없습니다
Is the answer correct or not?
답이 맞는지 틀린지?
concept?
개념?
Yes.
예.
Is your name Huang Zicheng?
당신의 이름이 Huang Zicheng 입니까?
Yes
예
are you a man?
당신은 남자입니까?
It is clear
분명하다
Yes
예
Are you the President of the United States?
당신은 미국 대통령입니까?
Actual electricity consumption
실제 소비전력
every time i make a mistake
내가 실수할 때마다
Electricity bill doubled
전기요금이 두배로 나오네요
Kind tips
친절한 팁
Are you the President of the United States?
당신은 미국 대통령입니까?
No
아니요
Data is extracted
데이터가 추출됩니다
you can start
당신은 시작할 수 있습니다
Let's get started
시작하자
Is Yaoyao your partner?
Yaoyao가 당신의 파트너인가요?
Yes
예
really
정말
Have you told anyone?
누구한테 말했어?
Online homework?
온라인 숙제?
No
아니요
forged
서서히 나아가는
No, not there
아니요, 거기는 아니에요
from
~에서
I can't answer
나는 대답할 수 없다
to answer your question
귀하의 질문에 답변하기 위해
the third time
세 번째
current
현재의
8 times the starting condition
시작 조건의 8배
I have I have
나는 가지고 있다
I have a friend named Jiang Xiaohua
내겐 장샤오화(Jiang Xiaohua)라는 친구가 있어요.
She also knows
그녀도 알고 있어요
Did you tell her?
그녀에게 말했어요?
Mission content?
미션 내용?
No
아니요
Really?
정말?
Have you received any special training?
특별한 훈련을 받은 적이 있나요?
Yes.
예.
really
정말
Do you know what a sample is?
샘플이 무엇인지 아시나요?
No
아니요
really
정말
Are you a CIA agent?
CIA 요원이신가요?
Yes
예
really
정말
Are you workers of your planet?
당신은 지구의 노동자입니까?
Yes
예
really
정말
Are you an agent of the Chinese Security Bureau?
당신은 중국 보안국의 요원입니까?
Yes
예
really
정말
Is it between you and Yaoyao?
당신과 Yaoyao 사이에 있습니까?
Between you and Yaoyaoyao
너와 야오야오야오 사이
No
아니요
really
정말
Do you love her?
당신은 그녀를 사랑합니까?
No
아니요
forged
서서히 나아가는
i kinda like her
나 그 사람 좀 좋아해
Did you hide the sample?
샘플을 숨겼나요?
In your eyes?
눈에?
Yes
예
really
정말
Are you still not satisfied?
아직도 만족하지 못하시나요?
I have no choice
어쩔수없이
are you serious?
너 진심이야?
very difficult
매우 어렵다
remember
기억하다
as long as i tell the truth
내가 진실을 말하는 한
there will be no pain
고통은 없을 거야
admit defeat
패배를 인정하다
Where are the samples hidden?
샘플은 어디에 숨겨져 있나요?
Sample is hidden
샘플이 숨겨져 있습니다.
In the kitchen trash can
주방 쓰레기통에
any trash can
아무 쓰레기통이라도
I don't remember either
나도 기억이 안 나
in the kitchen anyway
어쨌든 부엌에서
Are samples hidden?
샘플이 숨겨져 있나요?
kitchen in cafe
카페의 주방
Yes
예
really
정말
I can take you to find it
당신을 데려가서 찾아볼 수 있어요
but in you
하지만 당신 안에는
Let Yaoyao go first
야오야오를 먼저 놔두세요
you really love your partner
당신은 당신의 파트너를 정말 사랑합니다
I hid that thing
난 그걸 숨겼어
You can't hurt her
당신은 그녀를 다치게 할 수 없습니다
OK
좋아요
Are you OK?
괜찮으세요?
I am fine
괜찮아요
I told you
내가 말했잖아
Where do you hide your stuff?
당신은 물건을 어디에 숨겼나요?
do you remember?
기억 나니?
I remember
기억해
Guangtu is coming
광투가 온다
Are you a dummy?
당신은 더미입니까?
Do not you know me?
당신은 나를 모르나요?
Who are you
누구세요
sorry
죄송합니다
I was wrong
내가 틀렸어
Sorry, I was wrong
미안해, 내가 틀렸어
Hurry up
서둘러요
Go quickly
빨리 가세요
back door
뒷문
God I'm so tired
맙소사 나 너무 피곤해
look
바라보다
Great, you succeeded again
좋아요, 또 성공하셨어요
let's go
갑시다
Is this it?
이게 다야?
perhaps
아마도
let's go
갑시다
Do you love her?
당신은 그녀를 사랑합니까?
No
아니요
forged
서서히 나아가는
i kind of like him
나 그 사람 좀 좋아해
Did they ask you?
그들이 당신에게 물어봤나요?
this problem
이 문제
How did you answer?
어떻게 대답하셨나요?
I
나
Congratulations to both of you
두 분 모두 축하드립니다
You have completed this e-task
이 e-과제를 완료했습니다.
I passed
나는 통과 했어
why is it you again?
또 왜 그래?
Now
지금
Can you give me samples?
샘플을 주실 수 있나요?
this existence
이 존재
But no cryopreservation
하지만 냉동보관은 안됨
I don't know if it can be used
사용할 수 있을지는 모르겠지만
The mission of these tools
이 도구의 임무
among these tools
이 도구들 중에서
I've dealt with you many times
나는 당신을 여러 번 다루었습니다.
I do not know who you are
나는 네가 누군지 모른다
I am a private employee
나는 개인 직원이다
perform special mission
특별한 임무를 수행하다
Tony
토니
i can be a thai policeman
나도 태국 경찰이 될 수 있어요
CIA
CIA
it is a planet
그것은 행성이다
maybe china
아마도 중국
this means
이것은 의미한다
These people are all actors
이 사람들은 다 배우야
unnecessary
불필요한
this may be true
이게 사실일 수도 있어
No
아니요
this game is cool
이 게임은 멋지다
Every interview is personal
모든 인터뷰는 개인적입니다
you need to lie
거짓말을 해야 해
we use
우리는 사용
CIA standards
CIA 표준
trial
재판
this is an important part
이건 중요한 부분이에요
important part
중요한 부분
This is a double test
이것은 이중 테스트입니다.
double test
이중 테스트
special mission
특별 임무
the most important thing
가장 중요한 것
it's bringing back the truth
그것은 진실을 다시 가져오는 거야
this is amazing
이거 엄청나 네
All are online challenges
모두 온라인 챌린지입니다
You must try it
당신은 그것을 시도해야합니다
Really good
정말 좋다
if there is no partner
파트너가 없으면
I won't be able to get over this
난 이걸 극복할 수 없을 거야
The following two answers
다음 두 가지 답변
difficulty will increase
난이도가 높아지게 됩니다
this means
이것은 의미한다
you are closer
당신은 더 가깝습니다
Another step
또 다른 단계
looking forward to it
그것을 기대하고있다
Do you have any opinion
당신은 어떤 의견이 있습니까?
Nice scene
좋은 장면
you have put in a lot of effort
당신은 많은 노력을 기울였습니다
This game was really designed
이 게임은 정말 디자인됐어요
deadly specimen lies
치명적인 표본 거짓말
and this
이
thai police
태국 경찰
many moments
많은 순간들
I thought this was a real event
진짜 이벤트인줄 알았는데
it's like
그것은 같다
Zhou Min's world
주민의 세계
Do you think this is true?
이것이 사실이라고 생각하시나요?
In fact, everything has been arranged
사실 다 정리됐어
you are right
당신 말이 맞아요
after that
이후
It's getting harder and harder
점점 더 힘들어지네요
Will you continue?
계속하시겠습니까?
nature
자연
I'm addicted to playing
나는 노는 것에 중독됐다.
Me too
저도요
I started to look forward to
기대가 되기 시작했어요
at the next stage
다음 단계에서
Where are we going now?
우리는 지금 어디로 가는 걸까요?
Now
지금
Let's hide the stress
스트레스를 숨겨보자
I will accompany you until the end
끝까지 동행하겠습니다
let's go
갑시다
they succeeded
그들은 성공했다
OK
좋아요
Be prepared to tidy up
정리할 준비를 하세요.
truly special mission
정말 특별한 임무
OK
좋아요
Pull out the violin statue
바이올린 조각상을 꺼내세요
welcome
환영
you
너
sit
앉다
you have done your job
당신은 당신의 일을 다했습니다
Did you bring any money?
돈 좀 가져왔나요?
Yes
예
twenty thousand
이만
here
여기
And one more thing
그리고 하나 더
no thanks
고맙지 만 사양 할게
Hi pretty girl
안녕 이쁜 소녀 야
drink
마시다
I don't drink
나는 술을 마시지 않는다
don't worry
괜찮아요
drink
마시다
leave me
나를 떠나
Are you drunk?
취했나요?
a lot of money
많은 돈
Beautiful where are you going?
예쁘다 어디 가?
give me the bag
나에게 가방을 줘
leave me
나를 떠나
Why did you steal my bag?
왜 내 가방을 훔쳤어요?
I'm going out
내가 외출 해요
Sir, please leave quickly.
선생님, 빨리 나가주세요.
Who are you
누구세요
Brother Wei
웨이 형제
I want to ask you something
물어보고 싶은 게 있어요
Who are you
누구세요
that girl
그 소녀
Why are you looking for me?
왜 나를 찾고 있나요?
which girl
어느 여자
the girl who just left
방금 떠난 그 소녀
She's here to apply for a passport
그녀는 여권을 신청하러 왔습니다
Do you know about fake certificates?
가짜 인증서에 대해 알고 계시나요?
he's done it before
그 사람은 전에도 해봤어
Fake National Security Investigation Certificate
위조 국가보안법 수사증명서
he was arrested
그는 체포됐다
Make fake passports
가짜 여권 만들기
he might run away
그 사람은 도망갈지도 몰라
unable to sit down
앉을 수 없다
He can't bear the psychological pressure
정신적 압박을 견디지 못해서
That's why it's risky
그렇기 때문에 위험해요
Do you think anything is mine?
뭐든 내 것 같아요?
You guess there's something wrong with her
그녀에게 뭔가 문제가 있는 것 같군요
Maybe I've known it for a long time
어쩌면 나는 그것을 오랫동안 알고 있었을지도 모른다.
why are you there
왜 거기 있어?
After quarreling with you
너랑 다투고 나면
I'll go out and calm down
나가서 진정할게
I saw you coming out
네가 나오는 걸 봤어
what happened?
무슨 일이에요?
How did you get to this place?
어떻게 이곳에 왔나요?
I went to buy a passport
여권을 사러 갔어요
I went and bought a fake passport
가서 가짜 여권을 샀어요
you are crazy
너는 미쳤어
yes i'm crazy
그래 난 미쳤어
if i don't leave
내가 떠나지 않으면
i will lose my mind
나는 정신을 잃을 것이다
Can you calm down a little?
좀 진정할 수 있나요?
I can't calm down
진정할 수 없어
what have you done?
당신은 무엇을 했나요?
I
나
You stole the lab sample
당신은 실험실 샘플을 훔쳤습니다
say it again
다시 말해봐
I said I stole it
내가 훔쳤다고 했어
laboratory samples
실험실 샘플
What's your job?
당신의 직업은 무엇입니까?
Do not ask
묻지 마세요
I'm a mess now
난 지금 엉망이야
you have committed a crime
당신은 범죄를 저질렀습니다
they can catch me anytime
그 사람들은 언제든지 날 잡을 수 있어
so i'm leaving
그래서 난 떠난다
I'll leave now
나는 지금 떠날 것이다
If I didn't have a passport I would run away
여권이 없었다면 도망쳤을 것이다.
under any circumstances
어떤 경우 에라도
I have to get out of here
난 여기서 나가야 해
you can't leave
넌 떠날 수 없어
Would you think so if you went out?
나가면 그렇게 생각하겠어요?
go out
나가
what happened
무슨 일이에요
Tian Yang
양 티안
Listen, Yu Xiaoyu
들어봐, 유샤오유
confess something to me
나한테 뭐라도 고백해봐
Sample theft
샘플 도난
I have no choice
어쩔수없이
I now how to do?
이제 어떻게 해야 할까요?
They withheld my passport
그들은 내 여권을 압류했어요
They know I stole it
내가 훔친 걸 그 사람들은 알아
what should I do?
어떻게 해야 합니까?
something for me
나를 위한 뭔가
please give me something
나에게 뭔가를 주세요
Please help me
도와주세요
I beg you
부탁드립니다
Why did you do this?
왜이 짓을 했나요?
they are threatening me
그들이 나를 위협하고 있어요
from
~에서
gentlemen
신사
That is, professor
즉, 교수님
he is professor
그는 교수이다
professor
교수
I have published
나는 출판했다
in foreign newspapers
외국 신문에서
Use experimental data
실험 데이터 사용
Experimental data
실험 데이터
He threatened me with this
그는 이런 말로 나를 협박했다
He asked me to help him
그 사람이 나한테 도와달라고 했어요
For more data, see the Institute
더 많은 데이터는 연구소를 참조하세요.
so i took
그래서 내가 가져갔어
I thought I would take it with me
그걸 가지고 갈 줄 알았는데
I have no expectations
나는 기대가 없다
he is threatening me
그 사람이 나를 위협하고 있어요
He asked me to steal samples
그 사람이 나한테 샘플을 훔쳐오라고 했어
Yu Xiaoyu
유 샤오유
You better steal secrets to escape
탈출하려면 비밀을 훔치는 게 좋을 거야
worth
가치
I
나
I want to go out
나 나가고 싶어
I have a
나는
Admission Notice from British Columbia, Australia
호주 브리티시 컬럼비아의 입학 통지서
I have to go
나는 가야 해
Do you think you can leave?
떠날 수 있을 것 같아?
Why can't I leave?
왜 떠날 수 없나요?
I have a passport
나는 여권을 가지고 있다
no benefit
이익이 없다
look by youself
스스로 봐라
not even there
거기에도 없어
there is nothing
아무것도 없다
How could it be true?
어떻게 그것이 사실일 수 있습니까?
You can't even get through customs
세관 통과도 못해요
impossible
불가능한
I'm done
난 끝났어
There is only one way now
이제 방법은 하나뿐이다
what is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
I admit
나는 인정한다
I admit?
인정해요?
Do you want me to turn myself in?
내가 직접 제출하길 원하시나요?
I do not want
하고 싶지 않다
I can't go to jail
난 감옥에 갈 수 없어
i'm in jail
난 감옥에 있어요
If you can recover the sample
샘플을 회수할 수 있다면
If no loss is caused
손실이 발생하지 않은 경우
He will not be sentenced to death
그는 사형을 선고받지 않을 것이다
implement?
구현하다?
I will be sentenced to death
나는 사형을 선고받을 것이다
i have to give up
난 포기해야 해
something for me
나를 위한 뭔가
do you hate me?
당신은 날 싫어합니까?
i know you hate me
당신이 나를 싫어한다는 걸 알아요
I would rather die
차라리 죽는 게 낫겠어
don't let me go
나를 놓아주지 마세요
Yu Xiaoyu
유 샤오유
you made it yourself
당신이 직접 만들었어요
Surrender is your only option
항복만이 유일한 선택이다
No
아니요
I don't want to give up on myself
나는 나 자신을 포기하고 싶지 않다
Why should I give up?
왜 포기해야 합니까?
I give up I want to go to jail
포기한다 감옥에 가고 싶다
I don't want to go to jail
나는 감옥에 가고 싶지 않아요
How many years should I go to jail?
몇 년 동안 감옥에 가야 합니까?
i have grown up
나는 성장했다
my life will end
내 인생은 끝날 것이다
I don't want to go to jail
나는 감옥에 가고 싶지 않아요
Don't they know it yet?
그들은 아직 그것을 모르나요?
something for me
나를 위한 뭔가
They haven't discovered this yet
그들은 아직 이것을 발견하지 못했습니다
Do not say
말 하지마
Please help me
도와주세요
I don't want to go to jail
나는 감옥에 가고 싶지 않아요
please
제발
help me
도와주세요
I really don't want to go to jail
난 정말 감옥에 가고 싶지 않아요
I really
나는 정말
something for me
나를 위한 뭔가
Didn't you say you love me?
나를 사랑한다고 말하지 않았나요?
Didn't you say that?
그렇게 말하지 않았나요?
you will love me forever
당신은 나를 영원히 사랑할 것입니다
help me
도와주세요
I really don't want to go to jail
난 정말 감옥에 가고 싶지 않아요
please
제발
if you listen to me
당신이 내 말을 듣는다면
How did you get to this point today?
오늘 어떻게 여기까지 오셨나요?
everything i do
모든 것을 내가 할
You do everything yourself
당신은 모든 것을 스스로합니다.
think about it
그것에 대해 생각해보세요
In order to gain recognition, there is another way to survive
인정받기 위해서는 또 다른 생존방법이 있다
Escape is a road to death
탈출은 죽음으로 가는 길이다
Blackfish will throw you into the sea
Blackfish가 당신을 바다에 던질 것입니다
Or sell you abroad
아니면 해외에 팔아요
you got me involved
너 때문에 나한테 연루됐어
If I run away I'm guilty
도망치면 난 유죄야
I'll help you write the topic
주제 작성을 도와드릴게요
Help you clarify relationships and join the group
관계를 명확히 하고 그룹에 참여하도록 도와주세요.
everything i do
모든 것을 내가 할
He will make me your partner
그 사람이 나를 당신의 파트너로 만들어 줄 거예요
Yu Xiaoyu
유 샤오유
you always think about yourself
당신은 항상 자신에 대해 생각
Don't consider other people's feelings at all
다른 사람의 감정을 전혀 고려하지 마십시오
Come on, Yu Xiaoyu
자, 유샤오유
let me ask you
내가 너에게 물어볼께
Have you ever thought about your mother?
어머니에 대해 생각해 본 적 있나요?
you didn't miss me
당신은 나를 그리워하지 않았다
do not speak
말하지 않는다
She hopes to stay in Tianhai
그녀는 Tianhai에 머물기를 희망합니다.
Go to the Institute
연구소로 이동
One day I will bring her here
어느 날 나는 그녀를 여기로 데려올 것이다
But what are you thinking?
그런데 당신은 무슨 생각을 하고 있나요?
Live streaming is very popular
실시간 스트리밍이 매우 인기가 높습니다.
Travel abroad and be surrounded by gold
해외여행을 떠나 금빛에 둘러싸이세요
He met a rich and handsome man
그는 돈 많고 잘생긴 남자를 만났어요
And your bag
그리고 당신의 가방
because of your arrogance
너의 오만함 때문에
if you don't want to go to jail
감옥에 가고 싶지 않다면
There are only two ways
방법은 딱 두 가지뿐이에요
Either surrender
항복하거나
or you die
아니면 당신이 죽는다
Shri leaves
쉬리는 떠난다
He carefully observed Xiao Yue's situation
그는 Xiao Yue의 상황을 주의 깊게 관찰했습니다.
let's leave now
지금 떠나자
Are you worried about Yu Xiaoyu?
Yu Xiaoyu가 걱정되나요?
What's in it for me?
나에게 무엇이 들어있나요?
she is the only one
그녀는 유일한 사람이야
Now is the last straw to save her
이제 그녀를 구할 마지막 지푸라기야
I also fell
나도 떨어졌어
Yu Xiaoyu was seriously injured
유샤오위는 심각한 부상을 입었다
accept espionage organization
간첩조직을 받아들이다
and lawyer
그리고 변호사
This leads us to
이는 우리를 다음으로 이끈다.
serious losses
심각한 손실
and gain political rights
정치적 권리도 얻고
property
재산
He was sentenced to 10 years in prison
그는 징역 10년을 선고받았다.
Life imprisonment or death penalty
무기징역 또는 사형
I don't want to go to jail
나는 감옥에 가고 싶지 않아요
I don't want to face this world
나는 이 세상에 직면하고 싶지 않다
Don't tell my mother the truth
엄마한테 사실대로 말하지 마세요
Message from Yu Xiaoyu
Yu Xiaoyu의 메시지
something went wrong
뭔가 잘못됐어
I don't want to go to jail
나는 감옥에 가고 싶지 않아요
I don't want to face this world
나는 이 세상에 직면하고 싶지 않다
Don't tell my mother the truth
엄마한테 사실대로 말하지 마세요
you will die
당신은 죽을 것이다
call the ambulance
구급차를 불러주세요
OK
좋아요
Yu Xiaoyu
유 샤오유
Xiao Chen turns off the gas light
샤오첸은 가스등을 끈다
OK
좋아요
open the door
문을 열어라
Yu Xiaoyu
유 샤오유
I woke up
나는 일어났다
Yu Xiaoyu woke up
깨어난 유샤오유
When will the ambulance arrive?
구급차는 언제 도착하나요?
Instantly
곧
Take it out first
먼저 꺼내보세요
Take her out quickly
그 사람 빨리 데리고 나가
Hurry up
서둘러요
Take it easy
진정하세요
something for me
나를 위한 뭔가
welcome
환영
We are Kimhae National Security Bureau
우리는 김해국가안전보위부입니다
we want to talk to you
우리는 당신과 이야기하고 싶습니다
Welcome to enter
입장을 환영합니다
What’s wrong with you
왜 그래?
there is nothing
아무것도 없다
I feel fever
발열이 느껴진다
Can you stand trial?
재판을 받을 수 있나요?
perhaps
아마도
sit
앉다
Yu Xiaoyu is in trouble
우샤오위는 고민에 빠졌다
did you know?
알고 있었어?
What's up with her?
그녀에게 무슨 일이 있는 걸까요?
suicide
자살
What did you say?
뭐라고 하셨나요?
she committed suicide
그녀는 자살했다
Is she dead?
그녀는 죽었나요?
Do you know why she committed suicide?
그녀가 왜 자살했는지 아시나요?
something for me
나를 위한 뭔가
Yu Xiaoyu committed suicide
우샤오위는 자살했다
Didn't you notice?
눈치채지 못하셨나요?
I never thought she would commit suicide
그 사람이 자살할 거라고는 상상도 못 했어
Did I send it to you?
내가 당신에게 보냈나요?
I sent you a message
메시지를 보냈어요
I don't know, I lost my phone
모르겠어요, 휴대폰을 잃어버렸어요
Where did you lose?
어디서 잃었나요?
I fell into the sea
나는 바다에 빠졌다
Did you go to her house today?
오늘 그 사람 집에 갔어?
Yes
예
Didn't you notice?
눈치채지 못하셨나요?
She is emotionally unstable
그녀는 감정적으로 불안정하다
I shouldn't force her
나는 그녀에게 강요해서는 안 된다
I shouldn't argue with her
나는 그녀와 말다툼을 하면 안 된다
I'm the one who hurt her
그 사람에게 상처를 준 건 바로 나야
What did you force her to do?
그녀에게 무엇을 하라고 강요했나요?
I advised her to surrender
나는 그녀에게 항복하라고 충고했다
Laboratory samples stolen
실험실 샘플 도난
how do you know
어떻게 알아?
She told me personally
그녀는 나에게 개인적으로 말했다
Why did you commit suicide?
왜 자살했나요?
she committed suicide
그녀는 자살했다
I
나
I have no idea
나는 전혀 모른다
what do you know?
당신은 무엇을 알 수 있습니까?
she was threatened
그녀는 위협을 받았다
Who are you
누구세요
gentlemen
신사
any professor
어떤 교수라도
I do not know him
나는 그를 몰라요
I only know
나만 알아요
She was conducting a study in Australia
그녀는 호주에서 연구를 하고 있었습니다.
When I was studying in Australia
제가 호주에서 유학할 때
that person
저 사람
in the process of disseminating information
정보를 전파하는 과정에서
one move
한 번의 움직임
Data and samples
데이터 및 샘플
then threaten her
그럼 그 사람을 협박해
Let her continue stealing
그녀가 계속 훔치도록 놔두세요
Data and samples
데이터 및 샘플
You have
당신은
contact number
연락처
Xiao Yueyou
샤오웨유
It was they who summoned them.
그들을 소환한 것은 바로 그들이었다.
you are her lover
당신은 그녀의 애인입니다
How could you not know?
어떻게 모를 수가 있니?
about this person
이 사람에 대해
I called a professor
교수님한테 전화했어요
with professor
교수님과 함께
Why
왜
Maybe I am against her going abroad
어쩌면 나는 그녀가 해외로 나가는 것을 반대할지도 모른다
I have a good job here
나는 여기서 좋은 직업을 가지고 있습니다.
steady development
꾸준한 발전
Why did you leave China?
왜 중국을 떠났나요?
I do not understand
난 이해가 안 돼요
but she didn't listen
하지만 그녀는 듣지 않았어
if you go
당신이 가면
you will break up
너는 헤어질 것이다
perhaps
아마도
Didn't you think of any other way?
다른 방법은 생각하지 않았나요?
accept
수용하다
Yes
예
I'm the one who hurt her
그 사람에게 상처를 준 건 바로 나야
Study abroad
해외유학
You need to post
포스팅을 하셔야 합니다
In Power Abroad magazine
Power Abroad 잡지에서
If you promise to help her first
그녀를 먼저 도와주겠다고 약속했다면
then
그 다음에
you must not steal
훔치면 안 돼
Search data
데이터 검색
data
데이터
he won't be there
그 사람은 거기 없을 거야
more and more
점점 더
Do you hate her?
당신은 그녀를 싫어합니까?
I hate myself
나는 내 자신이 싫어
It seems you really love her
당신은 그녀를 정말 사랑하는 것 같아요
Love her
그녀를 사랑해
but it changed
하지만 변했어
she is famous on the internet
그녀는 인터넷에서 유명해요
everything has changed
모든 게 바뀌었다
Play on her ego
그녀의 자존심을 가지고 놀아 라.
Yes or no
예 혹은 아니오
Who wouldn't be proud now?
이제 누가 자랑스러워하지 않겠습니까?
can you play?
놀 수 있어?
No
아니요
So be it
그러면 그렇게 해
Can't leave the city for the time being
당분간 도시를 떠날 수 없다
if anything
혹시라도
We'll always find you
우리는 항상 당신을 찾을 것입니다
Can you tell me?
나에게 말해 줄 수 있나요?
Xiao, is Xiao Yu dead?
샤오, 샤오위는 죽었나요?
he is still in coma
그 사람은 아직도 혼수상태야
Finally I'm back
드디어 내가 돌아왔어
let me clarify it for you
내가 당신을 위해 그것을 명확히 할게요
OK
좋아요
Do you feel cold?
춥다고 느껴지나요?
a little
조금
Wipe it too
그것도 닦아
welcome
환영
Huang Ziqing this afternoon
오늘 오후 황자칭
this afternoon
오늘 오후
You came back alone
혼자 돌아오셨어요
that player
그 선수
Not with him anymore
더 이상 그 사람과 함께 있지 않아
He came back by himself this morning
그 사람 오늘 아침에 혼자 돌아왔어
How will you treat them?
당신은 그들을 어떻게 대할 것인가?
we want you to know the truth
우리는 당신이 진실을 알기를 바랍니다
You are from the district office
당신은 구청 출신이다.
Don't you know this is in Thailand?
여기가 태국에 있다는 걸 모르셨나요?
What is he doing
그는 무엇을 하고 있나요?
we know
우린 알아
but not completely
하지만 완전히는 아니야
Already withdrawn?
이미 철회되었나요?
As far as I know, not yet
내가 아는 한 아직은 아니다.
This is good
이것은 좋다
do not you?
그렇지 않습니까?
Do you trust him?
당신은 그를 신뢰합니까?
Not Ye Wu's opponent
예우의 상대는 아니다
So we need to monitor more
그래서 좀 더 모니터링이 필요해요
from the night fog
밤안개로부터
Will look for it again
다시 찾아보겠습니다
already
이미
This is our breakthrough
이것이 우리의 돌파구입니다
we need to monitor
우리는 모니터링해야 해
Huang Zhicheng’s abacus
황지성의 주판
I have
나는 가지고있다
in game
게임 중
this matter
이 문제
It's not difficult for you
너에겐 어렵지 않아
let him continue playing
그 사람이 계속 놀게 놔둬
When one day he understands
어느 날 그 사람이 이해가 되었을 때
The horse stopped on the edge of the cliff
말이 절벽 끝에 멈춰 섰다.
Or you trust him
아니면 그 사람을 믿나요?
you have enough brains
당신의 두뇌는 충분해요
to resist spies
스파이에 저항하다
I've known you for a long time
나는 당신을 오랫동안 알고 있었어요
This is the first time I discovered it
이번에 처음 발견했어요
You are very reluctant to work
당신은 일하기를 매우 꺼려합니다
Psychological science doesn’t ask you to analyze
심리학은 분석을 요구하지 않습니다
your partner
당신의 파트너
you know
알잖아
this is the best way
이것이 가장 좋은 방법이다
you must be uncomfortable
너 불편하겠지
I'll get you a cup of coffee
커피 한 잔 사줄게
ok sit there
알았어 거기 앉아
You're welcome
천만에요
I can do it myself, come back
나 혼자 할 수 있어 돌아와
Hi brother
안녕 형제
Where did you play?
어디서 놀았나요?
Your phone is turned off
휴대전화가 꺼져 있습니다.
I went to Thailand
나는 태국에 갔다.
I just got off the plane
방금 비행기에서 내렸어요
Are you OK
괜찮으세요
don't mention it
그것을 언급하지 마세요
Let's go home and have dinner
집에 가서 저녁 먹자
Can I not go?
나 가면 안 돼?
No
아니요
if you don't come
당신이 오지 않으면
Lao Huang will go find you
라오황이 너를 찾으러 갈 것이다
I know I know
내가 알지
Laohuang serial port connection
Laohuang 직렬 포트 연결
I called him
나는 그를 불렀다
I tell you
나는 당신에게 말한다
Be nice when you come back
돌아오면 친절하게 대해주세요
I disappeared during this time
나는 이 시간 동안 사라졌다
he has a good opinion
그 사람 좋은 의견이 있어
OK
좋아요
see you tonight
오늘 밤에 보자
You must speak for me
당신은 나를 위해 말해야합니다
i will provide
내가 제공할게
Dad, I'm sorry
아빠, 미안해요
I shouldn't be missing
내가 빠지면 ​​안 돼
you should have
당신은 가지고 있어야
Send me abroad
해외로 보내주세요
What to do in Thailand
태국에서 해야 할 일
I am playing game
나는 게임을 하고 있다
another game
다른 게임
there is a game
게임이 있어요
Don't you want to play?
놀고 싶지 않아?
This time is different
이번에는 다르다
this is a new way
이건 새로운 방법이야
online
온라인
Offline again
다시 오프라인
it's just a game
이건 그냥 게임 일 뿐이야
if i go with you
내가 너와 함께 가면
Not the same thing
같은 것은 아닙니다
More exciting than before
전보다 더 흥미진진해졌어
The most important thing is the bonus
가장 중요한 것은 보너스입니다.
It happened several times before
이전에도 여러 번 이런 일이 있었습니다
How much higher?
얼마나 더 높나요?
We have to wait until he succeeds
그가 성공할 때까지 기다려야 해
so that we can get it
우리가 그것을 얻을 수 있도록
slowly
느리게
past
과거
has been arrested
체포되었습니다
marketing fraud organization
마케팅 사기 조직
This is in Thailand
여기는 태국이에요
how do you look
당신은 어떻게 보입니까?
very similar
굉장히 유사한
What is my photo?
내 사진은 무엇입니까?
in your heart
당신의 마음 속에
If you say I joined a cult
내가 사이비 종교에 가입했다고 말하면
Do you believe me?
당신은 나를 믿습니까?
There is no such possibility
그런 가능성은 없어
You do not understand
당신은 이해하지 않는다
And you want to ask
그리고 당신은 묻고 싶습니다
I do not want to talk to you
나는 너와 말하고 싶지 않아
Anyway, please remember
아무튼 꼭 기억해주세요
play games
게임을하다
money can be made
돈은 벌 수 있다
no risk
위험 없음
enough
충분한
You are becoming more and more like a cult
점점 컬트 닮아가네
Brown
갈색
Let's play online
온라인으로 플레이하자
I am now
나는 지금
he
그
Don't go to jail.
감옥에 가지 마십시오.
my uncle.
내 삼촌.
he knows what to do
그 사람은 뭘 해야할지 알아요
At most, you can cheat some money
기껏해야 돈을 속일 수 있습니다
fool with some colors
어떤 색깔로 바보짓을 하다
if you break the law
법을 어기면
It turns out not
그렇지 않은 것으로 밝혀졌습니다
this is correct
이게 맞다
What? this is correct
무엇? 이게 맞다
You believe everything my brother says
넌 내 동생이 하는 말 다 믿잖아
No
아니요
Can't you be by my side?
내 옆에 있어주면 안 돼?
and set fire to
그리고 불을 지르다
Why are you so evil?
왜 그렇게 사악합니까?
Okay, okay, let's not talk.
알았어 알았어 얘기하지 말자
let's drink
마시자
Dad didn't listen to him
아빠는 그의 말을 듣지 않았다
Don't you understand what good or bad words are?
좋은 말이 무엇인지, 나쁜 말이 무엇인지 이해하지 못하시나요?
Lao Huang has little drinking ability
라오황은 술을 거의 마시지 못한다
always like to show off
항상 자랑하는 걸 좋아해요
Looks like you can drink it
마셔도 될 것 같네요
do not give up
포기 하지마
let's go
갑시다